The world, what a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit, seize it,
raise your flag and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart. I know.
The brand new world
that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
The way in the tumble waves.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is what I am for.
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began.
Over streets of green and shores of sand.
Through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me.
Some days from where I'll finally see
the light I will search for everywhere?
There's actually a god?
And he lives on an island up here
that no one's allowed to walk on?
He does.
I'm sure that everyone noticed the
big sign that said Godland Skypiea.
That means this land is ruled
by the almighty God, Anaru.
God's name is Anaru.
He knows and sees everything.
He's truly omniscient.
Everything?
He keeps his all-seeing eyes
focused on everyone. Always.
For real? Like right now? Oh, yes.
I can't get over the size of those trees.
Wait a minute.
So they do have earth and ground up here.
I see.
A place we're not allowed to
go to no matter what, huh?
I've seen that look in your eyes before,
Luffy, and it always gets us into trouble.
When the lady says we can't go there
because it's sacred or whatever.
That's exactly what she means.
We cannot go there.
I am not letting you drag
me down with you this time!
No, hey?
I understand we're not
supposed to go there.
Come on?
You really think I'm the kind
of guy who would do that?
Yes, absolutely.
Hey, wait!
If this guy is God, then shouldn't
he forgive you no matter what you do?
Walking around on some forbidden island
doesn't seem like a big deal to me.
No.
Breaking any law set forth by our
Almighty is nothing less than sacrilege.
I guess it doesn't matter either way.
He'd go even if it meant
he'd die in the process.
Nami!
All right, let's go and find her.
We're wasting time.
You don't care about saving Nami.
You just want to satisfy
your twisted urns to
do the exact opposite of
what you've been told.
Those are the biggest
trees I've ever seen in
my life they've got to
be hundreds of years old.
That or things grow bigger
a few miles up in the sky
and they're so tall I can't
even see where they top out
Luffy we gotta get going oh
fine don't listen to me but
you're gonna feel awful if
something bad happens to Nami?
while you're busy stuffing your face.
The food will be here when we get back.
I'm right behind you.
Conis, I know this guy, and I could
be here all day waiting on him.
Could you tell me how to
get to the upper yard?
I gotta go help Nami.
But you don't know for sure.
About Nami, she might just be out in the
clouds and nowhere near the upper yard.
I mean...
I can't explain how devastating it could
be to us to incur the wrath of our god,
Eneru.
Somebody help me!
Oh, no!
Bastard, he took my prey.
Those voices, those
sounds, what were they?
Just give up!
You should do the same!
This boy is mine!
Not if I can help it.
But it doesn't look like you can!
Wait, what the...
Who are they?
Something tells me I
don't want to find out.
What's going on?
Hmm, so this is your old waver, huh?
You should take better care of it.
It's not ours.
We found it like that.
Would you like me to take a look at it?
Assuming it's fixable, I should
be able to do that for you.
I'm an engineer that specializes
in dialed ships, so I should know.
Oh, my God.
What the
You down there help please give me a ride
please you want a ride
but this is a one person
boat Please help me oh
I can't there's no room
either give me the boat
or I'll slice you up
Gorilla
No!
Is this Aniru's doing?
How dare you, Hartford!
Get down!
Die!
No!
Get some water tiles down here now!
The fire's spreading!
Form up! Salute!
What are the white berets doing here?
Oh no, something must have happened.
You are all warned to use extreme caution.
I've received word that
illegal entrants have
infiltrated Skypiea
through Angel Beach today.
There are reportedly seven suspects.
But do not worry,
you can help with our search and investigation
by reporting all suspicious activity?
Leave it to the white berets!
White berets!
Did you see that?
It appeared as if he was
talking to someone in the water.
He was probably delusional.
Would someone please shut that dog up?
He was most likely begging for his life.
Why did Inaru take care
of that guy himself?
Isn't that why he sent us
here in the first place?
We probably ran out of time.
Ran out of time?
Yet another group of illegal entrants
have already infiltrated Skypea again.
Old lady Amazon informed us that it's a
ship with seven blue sea dwellers on board.
Seven blue sea dwellers.
That's probably us.
We're here illegally.
But if you wish to
proceed you must first pay
the entrance fee of one
billion extra per person.
That is the law.
Because we didn't pay the entrance fee.
No way.
Seven heads looks like one
of us is gonna have to share.
What the heck is happening on this
island and who are those people?
This is crazy.
I need to get back to
the others to warn them.
I just hope I get to them
before it's too late.
Beat this one, Usa!
I don't think that'll be a problem.
See?
My cloud sculpture's so good,
it should be in a museum!
That's amazing!
That's the worst-looking
art I've ever seen!
Can you fix it?
I've never seen parts like these before.
Come on, just fix it already.
I'm sorry, but until I have a
chance to look at this closer,
I don't know if I can fix it.
Will you at least try?
Yes, of course.
It's like we have company.
You there, on the beach, don't move!
Does he mean us?
Hey, uh, why are they crawling? Who knows?
I mean, they've obviously got issues.
Because they're crawling
around like crabs?
Fight for rays!
Halt!
House! House?
House, gentlemen. So, so!
Speak our language, we can't understand
you! What are they? Soldiers?
Blue Sam said they have issues.
Well, look what we have here!
You must be the Blue Sea-dwellers who have
illegally entered the
sovereign land of Skypiea!
Prepare to have the weight of Heaven's
judgment brought down upon you!
You're calling them criminals?
Illegal entry? What's that?
Don't waste your breath making excuses!
Amazon, the woman who
stands at Heaven's Gate,
captured these very images
using her vision dial! No, wait.
That can't be.
I think this is all a big
misunderstanding, Captain McKinley.
They're not the criminals
you're making them out to be.
What do you mean by illegal entry?
Does this have to do with that
ridiculous $1 billion extol entrance fee?
Because we didn't pay her a thing.
But didn't that old lady say
we didn't have to pay it?
It's not like she tried to stop us.
Yeah, that's true! Enough!
There's no sense trying
to deny it! Now fuss up!
Don't worry, you need not
become panicked just yet.
According to Heaven's Judgment, illegal
entry is only an eleventh-degree crime.
Once you accept your punishment,
which will be minimal,
you become legal tourist on the
spot and may go about your business.
Well, you should have told us that sooner.
But before we accept, what exactly do
you have planned as far as punishment?
A mere slap on the wrist.
All you need to do is pay
ten times the entrance fee.
Of course, if you pay immediately, we'll
pretend this little episode never happened.
So,
10 billion per person times seven people
makes your total 70 billion extols,
cash only.
Wait, 70 billion extols?
That sounds like an awful lot of money.
How much is that in berries?
That's the currency used in
the blue sea world, right?
Today's exchange rates are
10,000 extols per berry.
Let's see, now there's 10,000
and you gotta carry the one.
Is there a decimal in there? Five?
70 billion extols is 7
million berries, genius.
Get real!
Do you realize how expensive that is?
After risking our lives
coming to this place,
why should we have to pay a stupid
fee just to enter your precious city?
We can't agree to that!
You brought this on yourselves.
If you had just paid the 700,000
berries in the first place,
we wouldn't be having this talk.
That's still way too expensive!
This is your first warning.
The White Berets serve under
the vassals of Almighty Inneru.
Arguing with us will only
raise the level of your crime.
Oh, whatever, man.
Let's forget these idiots.
We need to start looking for Nami.
I'm getting worried.
She may need my tender
affections right about now.
She didn't care about the right now.
Those weird guys from earlier somehow
knew about us coming to Skypiea.
That means Luffy and the
others may be in trouble.
Better hurry back.
I can't wait to ride this thing.
I hope you can fix it.
This waiver looks downright abused.
If I find out you're
responsible for this damage,
you're looking at a tenth degree crime.
Destruction of Sky Island
property by a Blue Sea dweller.
I'm sorry, Captain McKinley.
This is my fault.
I crashed the waiver, not him.
Yeah, besides, this thing's mine.
Is that right?
Sounds suspicious to me.
I was under the impression waivers
didn't exist in the Blue Sea World.
If this one was stolen from Skypiea,
the degree of your crime will increase.
It's not stolen!
Wanna fight about it?
Oh no, there's a whole group of people.
I hope they're not those guys from before.
Whoever they are, I hope Luffy's
not pulling any of his usual stunts.
Let's sit down and take a breather, okay?
Zoro, Luffy, Chopper, there's
no reason for us to...
Nami, baby!
I missed you!
Luffy!
Promise you won't start any trouble, okay?
Don't know if I can keep that promise!
Hey, Nami!
We need you to fork up
seven million berries
from your stash to pay
for all the fines we got!
Oh, good!
So we pay the fine and we're clear!
Did he say seven million?
What?
Oh, crap.
I was so worked up, I
forgot to hit the brakes.
Ouch.
Captain!
Hey, thanks for letting
me use your waiver.
I love the way it handles.
I'm glad you enjoyed it,
but more importantly,
do you realize how much
trouble you're in now?
Captain!
Guys, let's make ourselves scarce.
Aren't you going to finish
the fight you just started?
Trust me, this Enaru is not
someone we want to mess with.
Yes, quite.
And knocking out an official
is a crime of the fifth degree.
Once you're found guilty of
committing a fifth degree crime,
almighty Enaru will banish you to
the land of the drifting clouds.
How's that bad?
Land of the drifting clouds?
That sounds like fun.
It's a death sentence. You die!
They'll put you and your
ship on a small cloud.
And set you adrift in the sea with
no chance of rescue or escape.
You'll eventually die a
very slow and painful death.
It's terrible.
Interesting that must be why we
saw that ship fall from the sky.
Wait, what are you talking about?
Don't you remember that
galleon we saw falling?
The saint bris.
I think it was called.
For all we know that crew could
have been punished over 200.
A hundred years ago.
You criminals!
Do you scum know what
you've done to our captain?
Who cares?
Sanji, let me handle this.
Anything for you!
Don't take it so personally.
It was a lucky shot.
A lucky shot?
Completely unintentional.
You're lying!
No, I'm telling you the truth.
Can you blame a beginner for messing
up and nearly killing your boss?
That's weird.
It seemed like you had a
pretty good handle on it to me.
Shut up.
Oh, shit, Luffy.
The enemy's trying to trick them
into thinking it was an accident.
Don't blow it, okay?
All right.
Gentlemen, as important
as your investigation is,
perhaps it would be best to get
the captain to a doctor first.
Just a thought.
All right, the captain!
Now, there's no reason to panic.
Let's take him to my house.
We'll get right on that. Let's go.
Consider yourselves
under preliminary arrest.
Don't go anywhere. Got it?
Why are they crawling again?
Can't they just carry
them like normal people?
You guys saved my life, so I know
you're not as bad as they claim you are.
So take this chance and get out of here!
Wait!
I think we'd better take her advice.
When I was on the waiver, I saw it for
myself: an island filled with monsters.
Right?
So you You did exactly what
everyone was hoping you wouldn't do.
You mean the place we were
told to never ever set foot on?
And there's monsters?
Don't give him any ideas!
It's nothing to get excited about, Luffy.
The last thing we need is
to get involved with this.
Regardless, we're leaving.
Now let's go!
Ah, it'll break my heart
to be away from Conis,
but if that's what Nami wants, so be it.
If we stick around any longer, Conis and
Pakeya may get in trouble because of us.
That's true.
Those white berets will charge
them as our accomplices.
If we can escape now on our own, then it
shouldn't cause them any trouble, right?
After all, how can they be helping
us when they're with that captain?
Okay, that's the plan. Let's go.
Luffy, what are you doing?
Why are we running away?
They haven't done anything.
Whoever arrests them is an idiot.
Please, please hurry.
The Blue Sea Dwellers will never escape.
Can't you two argue on the boat? Come on!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Staying here equals more
trouble for everybody!
We're in trouble no matter what.
Save yourselves!
Please, go!
Just great.
Be careful, miss.
If you say anything to
defend these criminals,
I will consider you and
your father accomplices.
These people must be punished
to the full extent of the
law for all the abusive language
and deplorable violence.
I find them guilty of fifth-degree crimes.
In the name of almighty Inaru, you are
banished to drift into clouds for eternity.
I told you it was an accident.
Oh, forget it.
Harass them!
Just run, you can't win.
Fire the milky arrows!
Go, Nami, run, you think?
What the heck?
Clouds!
Viper Rays, attack!
Cool trick, mind if I try?
Whoa, you see his arm?
Look, he's all stretchy.
I hope he's okay.
Go away, Devil Fruit!
You are worse!
Piece of cake.
Nami, how's the money situation looking?
50,000 berries left!
50,000?
Were that broke?
Normally, that'd last
us a day or two at most!
What's the deal?
Why are we so poor?
Listen up, everybody!
Your captain has something to say!
Everyone on my ship needs to be
more good with money from now on!
So lead by example! Huh?
Eh, in any case, the Fighting Formation
B I taught them to use was successful.
There's that.
Really?
They defeated the White Berets.
Unbelievable.
At this altitude, the athletic ability
of Blue Sea-Dwellers usually decreases.
Those poor deluded fools.
Sorry, criminals, you
have no chance of escape!
You should have behaved and
done what I told you to do.
Of all of the upholders
of law here at Skypiea,
we white parades are the most lenient.
However, they are not nearly as forgiving.
Congratulations!
You are now considered
second-degree criminals.
You can try to cry for mercy,
but you will all be judged?
By the priest of Upper Yarn, Hesor!